<ModOps>
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <!-- Zenon Gramme -->
    <Text>
      <GUID>2145100104</GUID>
      <Text>Zenon Gramme, architect of modern energy</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>2145100105</GUID>
      <Text>Key figure in the field of energy. His inventions have revolutionized industrial production methods, providing factories with enhanced energy efficiency. Always at the forefront of innovation, he supports industries in their transition toward more efficient processes.</Text>
    </Text>
    <!-- Father Jozef -->
    <Text>
      <GUID>2145100106</GUID>
      <Text>Father Jozef, patron saint of the forsaken</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>2145100107</GUID>
      <Text>Known for his tireless dedication to the forgotten, he inspires hope and compassion, strengthening the bond among residents and improving the lives of the most vulnerable.</Text>
    </Text>
    <!-- Jeannine Toussaint -->
    <Text>
      <GUID>2145100108</GUID>
      <Text>Jeannine Toussaint, artisan of luxury</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>2145100109</GUID>
      <Text>A legendary jeweler, she embodies refinement and innovation in the art of luxury jewelry and watchmaking. Under her influence, artisans have perfected techniques that minimize material usage while significantly increasing their productivity.</Text>
    </Text>
    <!-- Louis Baekeland -->
    <Text>
      <GUID>2145100110</GUID>
      <Text>Louis Baekeland, genius chemist</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>2145100111</GUID>
      <Text>A visionary inventor, Louis Baekeland revolutionized the chemical industry by creating the first synthetic plastic. His genius paved the way for an era of innovative materials, forever transforming industrial manufacturing. The factories he influences see their efficiency skyrocketing and costs reduced, embodying the spirit of technical progress.</Text>
    </Text>
    <!-- Julien Moens -->
    <Text>
      <GUID>2145100112</GUID>
      <Text>Julien Moens, the father of philately</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>2145100113</GUID>
      <Text>He revolutionized stamps, elevating them to true treasures for collectors. Thanks to his influence, post offices experience unprecedented prosperity, boosting their efficiency.</Text>
    </Text>
    <!-- Antonin Depage -->
    <Text>
      <GUID>2145100114</GUID>
      <Text>Antonin Depage, humanitarian doctor</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>2145100115</GUID>
      <Text>Renowned doctor and humanitarian, improving healthcare and leading disaster relief efforts. His expertise boosts the health of your citizens and improves efficiency for your hospitals.</Text>
    </Text>
    <!-- Marie-Jeanne Libert -->
    <Text>
      <GUID>2145100116</GUID>
      <Text>Marie-Jeanne Libert, renowned botanist</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>2145100117</GUID>
      <Text>A renowned botanist and naturalist, she works tirelessly to study and protect the plant life of your islands. Her unparalleled expertise brings new opportunities for your botanical gardens and tourism.</Text>
    </Text>
    <!-- Jan Nauheus -->
    <Text>
      <GUID>2145100118</GUID>
      <Text>Jan Nauheus, master of chocolate</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>2145100119</GUID>
      <Text>A true pioneer in chocolate-making, he created and perfected pralines, delighting the elite and revolutionizing chocolate production.</Text>
    </Text>
    <!-- Rudolphe Queletet -->
    <Text>
      <GUID>2145100120</GUID>
      <Text>Rudolphe Queletet, architect of statistics</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>2145100121</GUID>
      <Text>A pioneering statistician and social scientist, he improves productivity and efficiency across all public services, optimizing workforce management and economic planning.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
</ModOps>
